LEONARD: Okay.
(Leonard:)We'll be back
as soon as we can.
(clears throat)
Okay, so what...
(Penny:)is solder?
(Sheldon:)I suppose I should
set this up.
(Sheldon:)Or would you like
to rob me of that, too?
(Amy:)Knock it off or I'll start
making W-H sounds
(Amy:)for words
that just have a W.
(Sheldon:)You wouldn't.
"Hwatch" me.
(Sheldon:)Fine. I'm sorry.
(Sheldon:)Thank you for
the thoughtful gift.
(Sheldon:)I really do appreciate it.
(Sheldon:)As you know, I had become
attached to my old laptop.
(Sheldon:)But I'm sure, in time,
that this one will...
(gasps)
Jeepers creepers,
that started up fast!
(Amy:)I thought you might
like it.
(Sheldon:)Look at the 4K resolution.
(Sheldon:)Next time we Skype,
I'm gonna count
(Sheldon:)all those nostril hairs.
(Amy:)Or you could just look
into my eyes.
(Sheldon:)But you only have two eyes.
(Sheldon:)You got a lot of nostril hairs.